Guide to the Blukis Onat Applied Sciences (BOAS), Inc. Papers 1968-2010
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
- North Fork Tolt Project, Preliminary Cultural Resource Study and Recommendations for Seattle Public Utilities (Water Department), King County: report., 1988 (Box-folder 9/6, Project 198707 (see also 199013))
- Snoqualmie River Flood Damage Reduction Study, Plan of Action for Cultural Resource Reconnaissance and American Indian Land and Resource Use for U.S. Army Corps of Engineers, King County: related documents and report., 1987 (Box-folder 9/7, Project 198708.1)
- Snoqualmie River Flood Damage Reduction Study, Plan of Action for Cultural Resource Reconnaissance and American Indian Land and Resource Use for U.S. Army Corps of Engineers, King County: project maps., circa 1987 (Box-folder 73/2, Project 198708.1)
- Mill Creek, South Aberdeen/Cosmopolis Flood Control, Cultural Resource Reconnaissance and Testing as part of Environmental Impact Statement for U.S. Army Corps of Engineers, Grays Harbor County: project map and reports., 1987 (Box-folder 9/8, Project 198708.2)
- Snoqualmie River Flood Damage Reduction Study, Cultural Resource Reconnaissance and Identification of Traditional and Contemporary American Indian Land and Resource Use for U.S. Army Corps of Engineers, King County: report (2 copies)., 1988 March (Box-folder 9/9, Project 198708.3 and 198812.1)
- Snoqualmie River Flood Damage Reduction Study, Cultural Resource Reconnaissance and Identification of Traditional and Contemporary American Indian Land and Resource Use for U.S. Army Corps of Engineers, King County: aerial photograph of project area., 1984 (Box-folder 75/8, Project 198708.3)
- RESTRICTED - Naches Lithic Scatter (Site CRO5-07-81), Excavation and Data Recovery Report for White River Ranger District, Mt. Baker-Snoqualmie National Forest, King County: black and white photographs, stratigraphic profiles, and report., 1987-1988 (Box-folder 57R/3, Project 198709)
- Wells Creek Small Hydroelectric Project, Cultural Resource Reconnaissance, Whatcom County: report., 1987 (Box-folder 9/10, Project 198710)
- Rainbow Timber Sale, Cultural Resource Reconnaissance, Wenatchee National Forest, Chelan County: report., 1987 (Box-folder 9/11, Project 198711)
- RESTRICTED -- Headwaters-Extension (FS #06-17-06-30) of Site 45CH208, Data Recovery from Headwaters-Extension in Lake Wenatchee Ranger District, Wenatchee National Forest, Chelan County: color negatives, correspondence, background documents, proposal and data recovery plan, field notes, radiocarbon results, photocopies of historic maps (1897), interview notes, and report (unbound)., 1897, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 57R/4-7, Project 198712)
- RESTRICTED -- Headwaters-Extension (FS #06-17-06-30) of Site 45CH208, Data Recovery from Headwaters-Extension in Lake Wenatchee Ranger District, Wenatchee National Forest, Chelan County: bound report., 1897, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 58R/1, Project 198712)
- RESTRICTED -- Headwaters-Extension (FS #06-17-06-30) of Site 45CH208, Data Recovery from Headwaters-Extension in Lake Wenatchee Ranger District, Wenatchee National Forest, Chelan County: USGS topographic maps with photocopies; polyester film site map with photocopies and overlays; excavation unit plots, feature and artifact drawings, paper and film; and paste-up figures for report., [1987-1988] (Box-folder 74R/1, Project 198712)
- "Grassers Hill" Parking Lot at Ebey's Landing National Historical Reserve, Cultural Resource Testing, Island County: black and white prints; field notes; project maps; and report., 1987 (Box-folder 9/12, Project 198713)
- Jenkin's Creek Park, Preliminary Cultural Resource Overview, King County: 3-page letter report., 1987 (Box-folder 9/13, Project 198714)
- Koma Kulshan Small Hydroelectric Project, Cultural Resource Assessment, Whatcom County: report., 1988 (Box-folder 9/14, Project 198715)
- Maryhill State Park, Cultural Resource Assessment, Klickitat County: report., 1988 (Box-folder 9/15, Project 198801.1)
- Maryhill State Park, Cultural Resources Background and Archaeological Testing, Klickitat County: report., 1991 (Box-folder 9/16, Project 198801.2)
- Maryhill State Park, Cultural Resources Background and Archaeological Testing, Klickitat County: correspondence; field and lab notes; site forms; paper and drafting film report illustrations; project diazo prints; color slides; photographic logs., 1988-1990 (Box-folder 10/1, Project 198801.2)
- Maryhill State Park, Cultural Resources Background and Archaeological Testing, Klickitat County: aerial photographs; diazo prints of aerial photographs and project maps; photocopied maps; transit data and field site maps., undated, 1955, 1971, 1990 (Box-folder 73/3, Project 198801.2)
- Two Logging Units, Cultural Resource Assessment for Lummi Business Council, Lummi Indian Reservation, Whatcom County: report., 1988 (Box-folder 10/2, Project 198802)
- 196th Street Road Improvement Project, Cultural Resource Assessment for Department of Public Works, Snohomish County: aerial photographs; color prints and negatives; report., 1983; 1988 (Box-folder 10/3, Project 198804.1)
- Smokey Point Road Improvement Project, Cultural Resource Assessment for Department of Public Works, Snohomish County: report., 1988 (Box-folder 10/4, Project 198804.2)
- Cushman Spillway Modification Project, Historical/Cultural Inventory for Tacoma Public Utilities, Mason County: background documents; field notes; correspondence; project maps; report., 1988-1989 (Box-folder 10/5, Project 198806)
- Spokane to Everett, Washington, AT&T Fiber Optic Cable Project, Class I Historic Properties Inventory: report., 1988 (Box-folder 10/6, Project 198808 (see also 198813))
- Spokane to Everett, Washington, AT&T Fiber Optic Cable Project, Class I Historic Properties Inventory: map copies with cable route marked., 1988 (Box-folder 75/9, Project 198808 (see also 198813))
- Ferndale Pipeline Project, Cultural Resources Evaluation, Whatcom County: ½ inch VHS standard video cassette including one specifically of trench stratigraphy., circa 1988 (Box-folder 79/1-4, Project 198809 (see also 198917))
- Ferndale Pipeline Project, Cultural Resources Evaluation, Whatcom County: black and white negatives and contact sheet; field notes; stratigraphic profiles on paper and polyester film; project maps on paper and polyester film., 1988-1990 (Box-folder 73/4, Project 198809 (see also 198917))
- Ferndale Pipeline Project, Class I Historic Properties Inventory of the Route, Whatcom County: report., 1988 (Box-folder 11/1, Project 198809.1)
- Ferndale Pipeline Project, Sumas to Cherry Point, Class III Intensive Field Inventory, Whatcom County: black and white prints and negatives; photographic log; correspondence; field notes; maps (photocopies and drafting film); project area diazo prints; report., 1988-1989 (Box-folder 11/2, Project 198809.2 (see also 198917))
- Ferndale Pipeline Project, Sumas to Cherry Point, Class III Intensive Field Inventory, Whatcom County: project diazo prints., 1988 (Box-folder 75/10, Project 198809.2 (see also 198917))
- Ferndale Pipeline Project, Sumas to Cherry Point, Class III Intensive Field Inventory, Whatcom County: 1 box artifacts (lithics)., 1988 (Box-folder 72/3, Project 198809.2 (see also 198917))
- Kalama, Washington, to Portland, Oregon, AT&T Fiber Optic Cable Project, Class I Historic Properties Inventory: report., 1988 (Box-folder 11/3, Project 198810)
- Tolt Eastside Supply Line No. 2, Water Pipeline, Cultural Resource Assessment for Seattle Public Utilities (Water Department), King County: report., 1988 (Box-folder 11/4, Project 198811)
- Snoqualmie Falls Hydroelectric Project FERC Project Number 2493, Cultural Resource Overview, with Beak Consultants, Inc., for Puget Sound Power & Light Company, King County: preliminary, draft, and final reports., 1988-1989 (Box-folder 11/5, Project 198812.2)
- Spokane to Everett, Washington, AT&T Fiber Optic Cable Project: site maps (paper and drafting film); photocopies of baseline maps., circa 1988 (Box-folder 76/1-4, Project 198813 (see also 198808))
- Spokane to Everett, Washington, AT&T Fiber Optic Cable Project, Class III Intensive Field Inventory for Cultural Resources: maps (diazo prints and photocopies)., 1988-1989 (Box-folder 11/6, Project 198813.1 (see also 198808))
- Spokane to Everett, Washington, AT&T Fiber Optic Cable Project, Class III Intensive Field Inventory for Cultural Resources: report., 1988-1989 (Box-folder 12/1, Project 198813.1 (see also 198808))
- Spokane to Everett, Washington, AT&T Fiber Optic Cable Project, Class III Intensive Field Inventory for Cultural Resources: correspondence; field notes; maps; site forms., 1989 (Box-folder 12/2, Project 198813.1 (see also 198808))
- Spokane to Everett, Washington, AT&T Fiber Optic Cable Project, Class III Intensive Field Inventory for Cultural Resources: color prints; black and white prints and negatives; photographic logs., 1989 (Box-folder 13/1, Project 198813.1 (see also 198808))
- Spokane to Everett, Washington, AT&T Fiber Optic Cable Project, Archaeological Testing and Monitoring: report., 1990 (Box-folder 13/2, Project 198813.2)
- Spokane to Everett, Washington, AT&T Fiber Optic Cable Project, Archaeological Testing and Monitoring: field notes; site forms; diazo print project maps and aerial photos; maps., 1989 (Box-folder 13/3, Project 198813.2)
- Spokane to Everett, Washington, AT&T Fiber Optic Cable Project, Archaeological Testing and Monitoring: maps; stratigraphic profiles on paper and drafting film., circa 1989 (Box-folder 73/5, Project 198813.2)
- Spokane to Everett, Washington, AT&T Fiber Optic Cable Project, Archaeological Testing and Monitoring: report master with original photographs and maps., circa 1990 (Box-folder 14/1, Project 198813.2)
- Snoqualmie Pass to Spokane, Washington, AT&T Fiber Optics Cable Route, Historic Survey: report., circa 1990 (Box-folder 14/2, Project 198813.2a)
- Nooksack Falls Report Review, Puget Sound Power & Light Company: correspondence., circa 1990 (Box-folder 14/3, Project 198814)
- Spokane, Washington, to Boise, Idaho, AT&T Fiber Optic Cable Project, Class I Historic Properties Inventory: report., 1989 (Box-folder 14/4, Project 198901)
- Six Bridge Replacement Projects, Cultural Resources Assessment for Department of Public Works, Snohomish County: correspondence; bridge data sheets; field notes; maps; report., 1989-1990 (Box-folder 14/5, Project 198902.2)
- Nine Bridges and Two Intersections, Cultural Resources Assessmen, for Department of Public Works, Snohomish County: correspondence; black and white prints and negatives; bridge data sheets; field notes; maps; report., 1989-1990 (Box-folder 14/6, Project 198902.3)
- Six Bridge Replacement Projects, Cultural Resources Assessment for Department of Public Works, Snohomish County: bound report., 1990 (Box-folder 14/7, Project 198902.4)
- Six Bridge Replacement Projects, Cultural Resources Assessment for Department of Public Works, Snohomish County: bridge data sheets; color prints; field notes; maps; report master with original photographs and maps., 1990 (Box-folder 15/1, Project 198902.4)
- Ash Way Reroute, Cultural Resources Survey for Department of Public Works, Snohomish County: black and white prints and negatives; field notes; maps; report master with original photographs and maps; bound report., 1991 (Box-folder 15/2, Project 198902.5)
- Henry Kwina and Realight Logging Units, Cultural Resource Assessment for Lummi Indian Business Council, Lummi Indian Reservation, Whatcom County: 4-page report., circa 1989 (Box-folder 15/3, Project 198903)
- Whidbey Island Naval Air Station Draft Environmental Impact Statement, Historic Resources Survey, Island County: report., 1989 (Box-folder 15/4, Project 198904)
- Walla Walla Vicinity to Spokane, Washington, AT&T Fiber Optic Cable Project, Class III Intensive Field Inventory for Cultural Resources, Asotin, Columbia, Spokane, Walla Walla, and Whitman Counties: correspondence; site forms; maps; report master with original photographs and maps and bound report., 1989 (Box-folder 15/5-6, Project 198907.1)
- Spokane to Walla Walla, Washington, AT&T Fiber Optic Cable Project, Surveying, Testing, and Monitoring, Asotin, Columbia, Spokane, Walla Walla, and Whitman Counties: artifact drawings; black and white contact sheets, prints, and negatives; color negatives, prints, and slides; and bound report., 1989-1991 (Box-folder 15/7-8, Project 198907.2)
- Spokane to Walla Walla, Washington, AT&T Fiber Optic Cable Project: diazo prints of project area; artifact drawings; maps including photocopies of historic maps for towns in project area such as Colfax, Colton, Marengo, Steptoe, Thornton, Turner, Uniontown, Waitsburg (1901, 1910, 1913, 1980); photocopies of aerial photographs; and stratigraphic profiles (preprinted "45KI23" not always struckthrough) include 45GA202., undated, 1901, 1910, 1913, 1980, 1990 (Box-folder 73/6, Project 198907.2)
- Spokane to Walla Walla, Washington, AT&T Fiber Optic Cable Project, Surveying, Testing, and Monitoring: artifact data sheets and drawings; black and white contact sheets, prints, and negatives; color negatives, prints, and slides; field notes; historic resources background documents; photo logs; monitoring plan; report master with original photographs., 1981, 1985, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 16/1-7, Project 198907.2)
- Ledgerwood Mammoth Site (45GA202), Spokane to Walla Walla, Washington, AT&T Fiber Optic Cable Project: correspondence including radiocarbon dating results., 1990-1991 (Box-folder 16/8, Project 198907.3)
- Ledgerwood Mammoth Site (45GA202), Spokane to Walla Walla, Washington, AT&T Fiber Optic Cable Project, Garfield County: black and white prints; report including copy with original photographs., 1991 (Box-folder 17/1, Project 198907.3)
- The Ledgerwood Mammoth Site (45GA202), AT&T Fiber Optic Cable Project, Garfield County: 4 ½ inch VHS standard video cassettes with 7 and 8 labelled October 1990 and 7 noting removal of overburden and excavations., undated, 1990 (Box-folder 79/5-8, Project 198907.3)
- Mountain Loop Highway Improvements, Cultural Resource Inventory, Mt. Baker-Snoqualmie National Forest, Snohomish County: notes; maps; report., 1990 (Box-folder 17/2-3, Project 198908)
- Proposed Sultan Basin Land Exchange, Archaeological Reconnaissance, Mt. Baker-Snoqualmie National Forest, Snohomish and Pierce County: black and white prints and negatives; color slides; map; report master with original photographs; bound report., 1989 (Box-folder 17/4-5, Project 198909)
- Skagit Hydroelectric Project Relicensing, Survey and Evaluation of Traditional Cultural Values, Properties, and Significance of the Project Area to Indian Tribes for Envirosphere Company and Seattle City Light (SCL): color prints and negatives; correspondence; maps., 1989 (Box-folder 17/6-7, Project 198910)
- Skagit Hydroelectric Project Relicensing FERC No. 553, Survey and Evaluation of Traditional Cultural Values, Properties, and Significance of the Project Area to Indian Tribes for EBASCO Environmental (Envirosphere Company) and Seattle City Light (SCL): Envirosphere and EDAW, Inc. proposals to SCL; contact logs; correspondence; meeting minutes; progress reports; and final reports., 1989-1990 (Box-folder 18/1-5, Project 198910)
- Skagit Hydroelectric Project Relicensing FERC No. 553, Survey and Evaluation of Traditional Cultural Values, Properties, and Significance of the Project Area to Indian Tribes, for Envirosphere Company and SCL: newspaper article; architectural plan for Swinomish Smokehouse Project; maps (figures from report)., undated, 1990 (Box-folder 73/7, Project 198910)
- Skagit Hydroelectric Project Relicensing, Survey and Evaluation of Traditional Cultural Values, Properties, and Significance of the Project Area to Indian Tribes, for Envirosphere Company and SCL: audiotapes from intertribal meetings., 1990 January 19, 1990 February 23 (Box-folder 79/9-19, Project 198910)
- Swinomish Reservation, Cultural Resources Assessment, Supplement to Mavor Project Survey 1989, Skagit County: report., 1993 (Box-folder 18/6, Project 198911)
- Pacific Power and Light Quarry Near Roosevelt, Washington, Cultural Resource Assessment, Klickitat County: field notes; maps; report., 1989 (Box-folder 18/7, Project 198912.1)
- Pacific Power and Light Quarry Near Roosevelt, Washington, Cultural Resource Assessment, Klickitat County:correspondence; addendum to report regarding rock cluster., 1989 (Box-folder 18/8, Project 198912.2)
- Silver Lake Lithic Scatter, CRO-02-52, Evaluation of the Prehistoric Cultural Resources, Darrington Ranger District, Mt. Baker-Snoqualmie National Forest, Snohomish County: color print; field notes; maps; report., 1989-1990 (Box-folder 19/1-2, Project 198913)
- Silver Lake Lithic Scatter, CRO-02-52, Evaluation of the Prehistoric Cultural Resources, Darrington Ranger District, Mt. Baker-Snoqualmie National Forest, Snohomish County: artifact drawings; site maps., 1989-1990 (Box-folder 73/8, Project 198913)
- Ruth and Swamp Creek, Field Activities and Survey for EBASCO Environmental Company, Mt. Baker-Snoqualmie National Forest, Whatcom County: narrative; field notes., 1989 (Box-folder 19/3, Project 198914)
- Proposed Westview Housing Project, Cultural Resources Survey, Lopez Island, San Juan County: correspondence; field notes; maps; report., 1989-1990 (Box-folder 19/4-5, Project 198916)
- Ferndale Pipeline Project, Cultural Resources Evaluation and Matrix for Evaluation and Treatment of Subsurface Cultural Materials Discovered during Monitoring for ARCO Western Gas Pipeline Company and Federal Energy Regulatory Commission, Whatcom County: proposal; monitoring plan; report., 1989-1990 (Box-folder 19/6, Project 198917.1 (see also 198809))
- Ferndale Pipeline Project, Cultural Resources Monitoring for ARCO Western Gas Pipeline Company and Federal Energy Regulatory Commission, Whatcom County: correspondence; daily monitoring logs; meeting minutes., 1989-1990 (Box-folder 19/7, Project 198917.2 (see also 198809))
- Ferndale Pipeline Project, Archaeological Testing of Proposed Stream Crossings for ENSR Corporation, Whatcom County: bound report., 1989 (Box-folder 19/8, Project 198917.3)
- Ferndale Pipeline Project, Archaeological Testing of Proposed Stream Crossings for ENSR Corporation, Whatcom County (continued): black and white prints and negatives; color prints and negatives; photo logs; report master with original photographs., 1989 (Box-folder 20/1, Project 198917.3)
- Ferndale Pipeline Project, Cultural Resources Monitoring Results, Whatcom County: correspondence; field notes; video logs; photo logs with black and white negatives; report master with original figures and bound report., 1990-1991 (Box-folder 20/2, Project 198917.4)
- San Rafael Canal Flood Control Project, Geotechnical Soil Analysis, for U.S. Army Corps of Engineers, San Francisco District, California: report., 1990 February (Box-folder 20/3, Project 198918)
- Naval Undersea Warfare Engineering Station Properties in Jefferson and Kitsap Counties, Archaeological Resource Assessment: correspondence; National Register of Historic Places forms for multiple sites; and report., 1979, 1982, 1985, 1990 (Box-folder 20/4, Project 199001.1)
- Naval Undersea Warfare Engineering Station Properties in Jefferson and Kitsap Counties, Archaeological Resource Assessment (continued): correspondence and National Register of Historic Places forms for multiple sites., 1979, 1982, 1985, 1990 (Box-folder 21/1, Project 199001.1)
- Indian Island Site 45JE16, Naval Undersea Warfare Engineering Station Properties, Emergency Site Review, Jefferson County: 3-page letter report., 1990 (Box-folder 21/2, Project 199001.2)
- Blaine to Everett, AT&T Fiber Optic Cable Route, Class I Historic Properties Inventory: report., 1990 (Box-folder 21/3, Project 199002.1)
- Blaine to Everett, AT&T Fiber Optic Cable Route, Class III Cultural Resources Survey: field notes; maps; background documents; report., 1990 (Box-folder 21/4-5, Project 199002.2)
- Blaine to Everett, AT&T Fiber Optic Cable Route, Class III Cultural Resources Survey, Traditional Cultural Properties: report., 1991 (Box-folder 21/6, Project 199002.2a)
- Blaine to Everett, AT&T Fiber Optic Cable Route, Cultural Resource Testing and Research: black and white contact sheet and negatives; correspondence; Class I proposal; summaries of meeting with tribal representatives; report master with original photographs and maps and bound report., 1990-1991 (Box-folder 21/7-8, Project 199002.3)
- Blaine to Everett, AT&T Fiber Optic Cable Route, Cultural Resource Monitoring: field notes; testing and monitoring proposals; impletmentation and verification forms; and report., 1990-1991 (Box-folder 22/1-2, Project 199002.4)
- Blaine to Everett, AT&T Fiber Optic Cable Route, Cultural Resource Survey, Testing, and Monitoring: field maps., 1990-1991 (Box-folder 22/3, Project 199002.2, 199002.3 and 199002.4)
- Blaine to Everett, AT&T Fiber Optic Cable Route, Cultural Resources: maps on paper and drafting film copies of project area., 1990-1991 (Box-folder 73/9, Project 199002)
- Riverbend Estates Development in Auburn, Cultural Resources Survey, King County: report., 1990 (Box-folder 22/4, Project 199003)
- Ebey's Landing National Historical Reserve, National Park Service Interpretive Project Signage Review for Monroe's Landing Wayside Exhibit, Island County: correspondence., 1990 (Box-folder 22/5, Project 199004)
- Green River Bicycle Trail, Cultural Resource Survey, King County: color prints and negatives; report., 1990 (Box-folder 22/6, Project 199005)
- Renton Apartment Development, Archaeological Testing, King County: correspondence and report., 1991, 2001 (Box-folder 22/7, Project 199006)
- Low Income Housing Development in the Birch Point/Point Whitehorn Area, Survey and Testing, Whatcom County: correspondence; field notes; map; site form; report., 1990 (Box-folder 22/8, Project 199007)
- Mather Memorial Parkway, Cultural Resource Inventory, Mt. Baker-Snoqualmie National Forest, Pierce County: black and white prints and negatives; field notes; field maps; Forest Service cultural resource site records; and report., 1990-1991 (Box-folder 22/9-10, Project 199008)
- 45SK31, Cultural Resources Testing, Swinomish Community Hall Building Expansion, Skagit County: report., 1990 October (Box-folder 22/11, Project 199009)
- Swinomish Marina Project's Compensation Wetland, Cultural Resources Survey, Supplement to Cultural Resources Survey of Swinomish Channel Marina (198602), Skagit County: report., 1990 October (Box-folder 22/12, Project 199011 (see also 198602))
- Whidbey Island Naval Air Station, Cultural Resources Survey of Proposed Housing, Island County: aerial photographs; color prints and negatives; correspondence; field notes; maps; and report., 1990-1991 (Box-folder 23/1, Project 199012)
- Tolt Water Filtration Plant, Cultural Resources Survey for Seattle Public Utilities (Water Department), King County: background documents; correspondence; field notes; maps; project drawings; request for proposal; technical proposal; and report., 1991 (Box-folder 23/2, Project 199013.1 (see also 8707, 9705))
- Tolt Water Filtration Plant, Cultural Resources Survey of Primary Acquisition Area for Seattle Public Utilities (Water Department), King County: report., 1992 (Box-folder 23/3, Project 199013.2 (see also 8707, 9705))
- Tolt Water Filtration Plant, Cultural Resources Survey of Primary Acquisition Area, Cultural Resource Assessment of a Potential Burial Area in the Vicinity of the Backwash Solids Disposal Study Area for Seattle Public Utilities (Water Department), King County: black and white prints and negatives; correspondence; field notes; maps; site forms; and reports., 1991-1992 (Box-folder 23/4, Project 199013.2, 199013.3 (see also 8707, 9705))